Guide to the Associates of the Stanford University Libraries Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Associates of the Stanford University Libraries records
1969-2007
SC0701
Associates of the Stanford University Libraries
Stanford University. Libraries. Associates
15 Linear feet
(32 boxes)
The collection includes administrative files containing correspondence, minutes, financial records, membership lists, and other materials, 1969-2006; program files on events, 1975-2007; printed materials such as newsletters, membership directories, keepsakes, invitations, calendars, and postcards, 1974-2006, with a few items from Library events prior to the formation of ASUL; scrapbooks of documents, clippings, and photographs on the history of ASUL, 1973-78; photographs, 1973-2004; and audiotapes and videocassettes, 1994-1998.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Provenance
The collection was transferred to the Stanford University Archives by the Associates of the Stanford University Libraries in 2007. Additional materials were received in 2010.
Information about Access
This collection is open for research; materials must be requested at least 48 hours in advance of intended use.
Biographical/Historical Sketch
The Associates of the Stanford University Libraries (ASUL), founded in 1973, was a support organization to the University’s libraries. In addition to raising money for library acquisitions, it hosted a number of programs, lectures and workshops that were free and open to the public. The association was disbanded in 2007 when its administrative funding was cut.
Description of the Collection
The collection includes administrative files containing correspondence, minutes, financial records, membership lists, and other materials, 1969-2006; program files on events, 1975-2007; printed materials such as newsletters, membership directories, keepsakes, invitations, calendars, and postcards, 1974-2006, with a few items from Library events prior to the formation of ASUL; scrapbooks of documents, clippings, and photographs on the history of ASUL, 1973-78; photographs, 1973-2004; and audiotapes and videocassettes, 1994-1998.
Access Terms
Associates of the Stanford University Libraries; Stanford University. Libraries.; Friends of the library--California
Collection Contents
- Administrative Files, Series 1
  - Organization of ASUL: Correspondence, proposed by-laws, etc., 1969-1973 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Minutes and other materials re early history, 1973-80 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Brief History of the Founding of ASUL, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Bylaws, 1973-83 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Bylaws, 1988-98 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Board, Advisory Council, 1980-86 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Board of Directors, lists, 1985-1997 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Policies of the Board of Directors, 1978-96 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Board minutes, 1973-75 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Executive committee minutes, 1974-75 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Board minutes, 1976-78 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Executive committee minutes, 1976-78 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Board minutes, 1979-80 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Executive committee minutes, 1979-80 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Board minutes, 1981-83 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Executive committee minutes, 1981-82 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Executive committee minutes, 1983-84 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Board minutes, 1984-85 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Board minutes, 1986-87 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Executive committee minutes, 1985-87 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Executive committee minutes, 1988-95 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Board minutes, 1988-89 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Board minutes, 1990-92 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Board minutes, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Board minutes, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Board minutes, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Board minutes, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Board minutes, 1997 Mar.-June (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Minutes (Board and Ex. Comm.), 1997 Oct. - 1998 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Minutes (Board and Ex. Comm.), 1999-2000 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Minutes (Board and Ex. Comm.), 2001-2003 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Minutes (Board and Ex. Comm.), 2004-2007 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Board minutes [computer disk], 2003-2006 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Board notebook: Bylaws (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Board notebook: Annual Meeting, 1976-83 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Board notebook: Financial State, 1974-82 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Board notebook: Membership, 1975-76 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Board notebook: Nominating committee, 1975-82 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Board notebook: Imprint and miscellaneous (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Annual meetings, minutes, 1976-79 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Annual meetings, minutes, 1980-88 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Annual meeting, minutes and materials re talk by John Felstiner, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Annual meeting, materials re talk by David Weber and his text, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Annual meeting minutes and correpondence, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Annual meetings, minutes, 1994-96 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - $100,000 endowment, 1987-88 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - $150,000 ASK project, 1994-95 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Access project, 1989-92 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Associates room (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - ASUL receptions, planning for, 1980-81 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - ASUL web site, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Author's Day Committee, minutes, etc., 1986-87 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Book Auction - George Fox, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Book Auction - receipt forms, completed (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Book Auction - samples forms (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Book Auction - records, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Book sales, 1991-92 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Book sales, 1997-98 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Centennial Fundraising, 1988-90 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, miscellaneous, 1979-89 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Committees, job descriptions for, 1983-85 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, miscellaneous, 1985-2003 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Cusick, Joe, chair, correspondence, 1995-96 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Cusick, Joe and Kathy, correspondence, 1973-1998 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Dallas Trip (includes snapshots), 1992 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Developmental proposal - workshop, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Display cabinets, estimate on, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Duffy, Philip G., correspondence amd acknowledgment of gifts, 1977-86 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Funds received, notebook, 1989-95 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Funds, History of, 1976-85 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Gifts to retiring library staff, 1985-2000 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Gifts to the Stanford University Libraries, 1976-2000 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Gifts to the Stanford University Libraries, listings, 1987-96 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Goff, Harry, treasurer (includes photo of Goff), 1994-2000 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Hanna, Rilla - correspondence, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Heyeck, Robin, clipping, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Hopkins room - assorted records, 1984-86 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Hopkins room - bills, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Hopkins room - correspondence, memos, etc., 1969-86 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Hopkins Room - estimates re work on room and furnishings, 1986-88 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Hopkins Room - inventories, 1997-99 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Hopkins room - re suppoena of [illegible], 1988 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Imprint correspondence, 1988-89 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Information Desk project, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Letter from SUL Directors, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Letters Home - ad for book by Nancy Nichols, circa 1993 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Liquor license, 1981-84 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Membership privileges, 1994-97 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Membership statistics, 1984-88 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Memoranda, 1977-95 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Message from the Chairman, 1970s-80s (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - New remit cards (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Newsletter production, sample material, 1997-98 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Nichols, Alan, Bd. member, correspondence, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Nominating committee, 1986-99 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Notebook: unidentified notes [possibly Sally Treadway] (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Published ephemera, List of, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Restricted fund history, 1982-86 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Rosters, 1981-85 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Sowers, Margaret (re her death and memorials), 1996 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Stanford Professional Publishing Course, 1998-99 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Strategic plan - revised, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Student book collection contest, 1977-85 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Tax data and info, 1984-91 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Van Camp,Anne - annual meeting, April, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Weber, David - Notes from, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Workshop of 1993: informational packet, working groups, minutes, notes (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Workshop of 1993: memos, email, and other documents (including "The Sad Tale of Bazouge" inscribed to Joe [Cusick] by Dorothy Hatch), 1993-94 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Wreden, Byra, correspondence and biographical, 1995-2000 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Wreden, William P., biographical with several notes from family, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Wreden, William P., miscellaneous works, 1949-90 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Membership card file, active members (Box 14)
  - Membership card file (dropped or deceased members) (Box 15)
- Program Files, Series 2
  - Adrian Wilson, Dec. 3, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Adventures of Mark Twain collector, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Andrew Hoyem, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Anniversary: 25th Celebration (includes photos), 1998 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Annual picnic, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Annual picnic, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Annual picnic, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Annual picnic, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Annual picnic, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Annual picnic and auction, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Art Library, Alex Ross, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Authors event of 1985, 1985-86 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Authors' dinner, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Authors!, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Beaudin, Fernand - Guttenberg Effect, Nov. 1990 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Big Band Era – Grover Sales, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Bohemian Club lunch, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Calligraphy workshop, Kitty Maguire, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Calligraphy workshop, Darle Maveety, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Canochan/Osborne/Comm. Art - French Revolution, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Charles Kerns, Media Center, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Chemistry and biology library tour, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Collectors Sundays, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Conservation Matters!, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Conversations with authors, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Developmental workshop, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Dickens trip, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Don Knuth's 3:16, talk and exhibit, March 1991 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Early American cultural history – Jay W. Flegelman, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Earthquakes – Amor Nur, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Faculty talk – David Abernathy, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Faculty talk - Ronald Bracewell, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Faculty talk - Gordon Chang, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Faculty talk - Alexander George, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Faculty talk – R. W. Lyman, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Faculty talk - Stephen Orgel, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Faculty talks, 1994-95 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Haskell Norman, Jan. 1991 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Hebraica & Judaica libraries – Roger Kohn (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Henry Lowood - Silicon Valley and Stanford, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Holiday progrram, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Holiday Program, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Holiday party, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Holiday Program, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Irish Renaissance program, Oct. 1990 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Joanne Sonnichsen, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Johanna Drucker, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - John Fowles, the nature of nature, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - John thomas, biology, March 1990 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Kevin Starr, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Librarians' luncheon, May 24, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Librarians' luncheon, Feb. 1990 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Lunch tennis club/International Antiq. Bookfair (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Map society meeting, Jan. 1991 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Medical talk, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Medieval Christmas party, 2003 Dec. (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Medieval pilgrimages, May 1991 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Meyer Library tour, May 1990 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Modernism in Literature, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Monterey - Carmel, May 1991 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Mystery film series, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Mystery Symposium, March 1991 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Norman Thrower on Columbus, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Philadelphia trip, Fall 1990 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Polish Artists books, 1997-98 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Roy Porter talk, oct. 31, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - San Francisco Antiquarian Book Fair, Feb. 1991 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - San Francisco field trip, May 1990 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Saroyan collection (1 of 3), 1996-97 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Saroyan collection (2 of 3), 1997-98 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Saroyan Collection (3 of 3), 1997 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Sonoma trip, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Sonoma weekend, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Sports History, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Stanford Bookstore, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Subscription series, Music Archives, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Sumner Stone, future of type design, 1995-96 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Susan Stephens, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Terry Bellinger, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Traditions of Science - Panofsky, January 1990 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Victorian & Edwardian collection, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Victorian Christmas, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - William Morris to Bloomsbury, 1999 Aug.-Sept. (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - William Peterson - Kelmscott Press, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Workshop revisited, 1993-1995 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Programs, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Programs, 1976-78 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Programs, 1978-79 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Programs, 1979-80 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Programs, 1980-81 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Programs, 1981-82 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Programs, 1982-83 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Programs, 1983-84 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Programs - Steinbeck weekend, 1984 May (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Programs (1), 1984-85 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Programs (2), 1984-85 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - programs, 1985-86 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - programs, 1986-87 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - programs, 1987-88 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - programs, 1988-89 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Programs, 1989-90 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Programs, 1990-91 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Programs, 1991-92 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Programs, 1992-93 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Programs, 1993-94 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Programs, 1994-95 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Programs, 1995-96 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Programs (part 1 of binder), 1994-96 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Programs (part 2 of binder), 1994-96 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Programs, 1996-97 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Programs, 1997-98 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - programs, 1998-99 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Programs, 1999-2000 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Programs, 2000-2001 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Programs, 2000-2001 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Programs, 2002-03 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Programs, 2003-04 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Programs, 2005-06 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Programs, 2006-07 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Printed Materials, Series 3
  - Newsletter, Vol. I-II, 1988 - 1990 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Newsletter, Vol. III-IV, 1990-1992 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Newsletter, Vol. V-VI, 1992-1994 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Newsletter, Vol. VII-IX, 1994 - 1997 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Ex Libris, Vol. 10, Winter, Spring, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Ex Libris, 1998/99 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Ex Libris, Fall 1999-Autumn 2001 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Ex Libris, Summer 2002 - 2002/03 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Ex Libris, Summer 2005, Fall 2006 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Membership brochures (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Membership directories, 1978-84 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Membership directories, 1985-87 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Membership directories, 1996-2006 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Calendars, 1978/79 - 1987/88 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Calendars, 1995/96 - 1999/2000 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Calendars, 2000/2001 - 2005/2006 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Keepsakes, programs, invitations, postcards, etc., 1954 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Keepsakes, programs, invitations, postcards, etc., 1956 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Keepsakes, programs, invitations, postcards, etc., 1962-68 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Keepsakes, programs, invitations, postcards, etc., 1971 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Keepsakes, programs, invitations, postcards, etc., 1974 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Keepsakes, programs, invitations, postcards, etc., 1975 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Keepsakes, programs, invitations, postcards, etc., 1976 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Keepsakes, programs, invitations, postcards, etc., 1976 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Keepsakes, programs, invitations, postcards, etc., 1977 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Keepsakes, programs, invitations, postcards, etc., 1978 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Keepsakes, programs, invitations, postcards, etc., 1979 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Keepsakes, programs, invitations, postcards, etc., 1979 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Keepsakes, programs, invitations, postcards, etc., 1980 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Keepsakes, programs, invitations, postcards, etc., 1981 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Keepsakes, programs, invitations, postcards, etc., 1982 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Keepsakes, programs, invitations, postcards, etc., 1982 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Keepsakes, programs, invitations, postcards, etc., 1983 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Keepsakes, programs, invitations, postcards, etc., 1984 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Keepsakes, programs, invitations, postcards, etc., 1985 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Keepsakes, programs, invitations, postcards, etc., 1986-87 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Keepsakes, programs, invitations, postcards, etc., 1988 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Keepsakes, programs, invitations, postcards, etc., 1990 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Keepsakes, programs, invitations, postcards, etc., 1991, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Keepsakes, programs, invitations, postcards, etc., 1996-97 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Keepsakes, programs, invitations, postcards, etc., 1998 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Keepsakes, programs, invitations, postcards, etc., 1999 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Keepsakes, programs, invitations, postcards, etc., 2000 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Keepsakes, programs, invitations, postcards, etc., 2001 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Keepsakes, programs, invitations, postcards, etc., 2002 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Keepsakes, programs, invitations, postcards, etc., 2003 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Keepsakes, programs, invitations, postcards, etc., 2004 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Keepsakes, programs, invitations, postcards, etc., 2005 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Keepsakes, programs, invitations, postcards, etc., 2006 (Box 19, Folder 14)
- Photographs, Series 4
  - Group 1: Events, 1995-96 (Box 20)
  - Group 1: New England Trip, 1996 (Box 20)
  - Group 1: England Trip, 1997 June (Box 20)
  - Group 1: Bloomsbury Trip volume 1, 1999 Autumn (Box 20)
  - Group 2: Bloomsbury Trip volume 2, 1999 Autumn (Box 20)
  - Group 2: Events, 2001-2003 (Box 20)
  - Group 2: Northern England trip, 2002 (Box 20)
  - Group 2: Northern England trip, 2002 (Box 20)
  - Small binder: Dickens trip, 1998 (Box 20)
  - Small binder: Events, 2003-2004 (Box 20)
  - Small binder: Events, 1974-86 (Box 21)
  - Small binder: Events, 1980 (Box 21)
  - Small binder: Events, 1993-98 (Box 21)
  - Small binder: Events, 1990-2000 (Box 21)
  - Photo box of event photos (mostly identified), 1976-96 (Box 21)
  - Small box of event photos (unsorted) (Box 21)
  - Photographs of events, unprocessed (Box 22)
  - Album: photos from events, 1983-84 (Box 23)
- Scrapbooks, Series 5
  - History scrapbook I (minutes, letters, printed materials, photos, etc.) (1 of 7), 1973-74 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - History scrapbook I (2 of 7), 1974-75 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - History scrapbook I (3 of 7), 1975 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - History scrapbook I (4 of 7), 1975 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - History scrapbook I (5 of 7), 1975 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - History scrapbook I (6 of 7), 1976 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - History scrapbook I (7 of 7), 1976 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - History scrapbook II (letters, publications, clippings, photos) (1 of 5), 1976 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - History scrapbook II (2 of 5), 1977 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - History scrapbook II (3 of 5), 1977 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - History scrapbook II (4 of 5), 1977 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - History scrapbook II (5 of 5), 1977 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - History scrapbook III (letters, publications, clippings, photos) (1 of 5), 1977 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - History scrapbook III (2 of 5), 1977 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - History scrapbook III (3 of 5), 1978 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - History scrapbook III (4 of 5), 1978 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - History scrapbook III (5 of 5), 1978 (Box 24, Folder 17)
- Audiovisual Materials, Series 6
  - VHS tape: Wally Stegner (Fran Schiff) (Box 25)
  - VHS tape: the Stanford and Silicon Valley project. SUL 1996 (Box 25)
  - VHS tape: The Arts at Stanford. The Spirit of Saroyan. Part 1, 1997 (Box 25)
  - VHS tape:The Arts at Stanford. The Spirit of Saroyan. Part 2, 1997 (Box 25)
  - VHS tape: "readingWriters" program #166. The Bread of Days (Cable Coop 6, Palo Alto), 1995 (Box 25)
  - VHS tape: CBS Sunday Morning. Segment on Yolla Bolly Press, 1995 March 12 (Box 25)
  - VHS tape: Life of the Mind. "The Nature of Nature" John Fowles [2 copies], 1996 (Box 25)
  - VHS tape: Beyond Words: New tools for the learning community. Stanford Learning Lab. (Box 25)
  - VHS tape:readingWriters rW168. John Felstiner. (Cable Coop Productions, Palo Alto), 1995 (Box 25)
  - Audiocassette: Adventures of a Mark Twain Collector. Claude S. Brinegar, 1997 Feb. 2 (Box 25)
  - Audiocassette: Jay Fliegelman "Storied Associations: Collecting Early American Cultural History.", 1996 Feb. 25 (Box 25)
  - Audiocassette: Gordon Chang, 1998 Mar. 19 (Box 25)
  - Audiocassette: Andrew Hoyem "Fit to Print", 1998 Apr. 20 (Box 25)
  - Audiocassette: Dr. Bortz, 1994 Mar. 13 (Box 25)
  - Audiocassette: Library Fair. Elizabeth Tallent, 1994 Oct. 2 (Box 25)
  - Audiocassette: 25th Anniversary Party, 1998 Oct. 27 (Box 25)
  - Audiocassette: prof. Stephen orgel, 1997 Nov. 11 (Box 25)
  - Audiocassette: Joel Leivick, 1995 Jan. 19 (Box 25)
  - Audiocassette: The Spirit of Saroyan (5 tapes), 1997 May 10 (Box 25)
  - Audiocassette: Library Assoc. Joyce Wilson, 1994 Feb. 13 (Box 25)
  - Audiocassette: sales tape (Box 25)
  - Audiocassette: Faculty Talks. David Abernathy, 1996 May 17 (Box 25)
  - Audiocassette: Adela Roatcap, 1995 Feb. 12 (Box 25)
  - Audiocassette: Ellsworth, 1996 April 18 (Box 25)
  - Audiocassette: Stanford Antiquarian Bookfair, 1985 October (Box 25)
  - Audiocassette: ASUL (Susan Shillinglaw), 1995 Sept. 20 (Box 25)
  - Audiocassette: Mike Keller, Internet. Annual meeting, 1995 May 2 (Box 25)
  - Audiocassette: unlabelled (possibly blank) (Box 25)
- Oversize Materials, Series 7
  - Keepsake: leaves from The Work & Play of Adrian Wilson, 1984 (Box 26)
  - Keepsake: Adrian Wilson 1923-1988 [biography], 1989 (Box 26)
  - Keepsake: The Friendly Hen [for joint meeting of ASUL and The Committee for Art], 1983 (Box 26)
  - Keepsake: The Psalms of David [on the occasion of Will Carter's Talk] (Box 26)
  - Certificate: ASUL honorary life membership to Cecil H. and Ida M. Green (2 copies), 1977 (Box 26)
  - Certificate: Stanford Associates extends congratulations to ASUL on the presentation of the 5 millionth book (Box 26)